Anna Culbert

DATA ANALYST

(515) 422-4445

AnnaRLourens@gmail.com

in LinkedIn

https://annaculbert.github.io/

Lafayette, Colorado

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Self-starter and driven entry-level data analyst blending a background of five years of professional experience in healthcare with the recent acquisition of analytical skills through the Google Data Analytics Certificate Program. Proven ability to work with data, communicate with team members and stakeholders, and create visualizations of findings to improve corporate performance.

SKILLS

SQL | Google Sheets | Microsoft Excel | Tableau | R | Data analysis | Data visualization Communication | Time management | Organization | Interpersonal skills | Adaptability

EDUCATION & RELEVANT COURSEWORK

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate

July 2021 - April 2022

A project-based class focused on developing skills to prepare, process, and analyze data for key insights; effectively share findings; and provide data-driven recommendations. See portfolio for more details.

Master of Occupational Therapy, University of Missouri - Columbia, Missouri
Introductory Statistical Reasoning, University of Missouri - Columbia, Missouri
Bachelor of Health Science, University of Missouri - Columbia, Missouri
August 2012 - December 2015

WORK EXPERIENCE

Occupational Therapy Team Supervisor

January 2022 - Present

Skills 4 Life Pediatric Occupational Therapy, Boulder, Colorado

- Managed team of employees, overseeing hiring, training, and professional growth of employees while managing personal caseload of clients
- Streamlined intake and documentation process during transition of practice ownership to boost productivity and improve daily workflow
- Created documents and other communications with use of Google Docs and Sheets

Occupational Therapist

November 2020 - Present

Skills 4 Life Pediatric Occupational Therapy, Boulder, Colorado

- Corresponded with parents of 20+ students on weekly basis to establish and maintain clear communication and ensure coordination of care
- Managed time efficiently to ensure timeliness of session start times, scheduling of meetings, and completion of additional responsibilities and research
- Coached elementary through college-aged students in effective executive function skills to exceed in time management, organization, and planning and prioritizing

Occupational Therapist

May 2019 - January 2021

Gateways Community Services, Nashua, New Hampshire

- Contributed to weekly meetings with knowledge and research to encourage positive and purposeful engagements between members of the therapy team
- Successfully problem solved in unclear therapeutic situations through research and analysis of client challenges and family resources
- Developed strong and trusting relationships with coworkers, families, and clients through clear communication, attention to detail, and positive engagements